噢  嘿  丽芙  你想来点巧克力布丁么
Oh! Hey, Liv, you want some chocolate pudding?
我们在冰箱里发现了一大碗
We found a big bowl of it in the fridge.
呃  二位  这可不是巧克力布丁
Um, boys, that's not chocolate pudding.
这是我的从巴黎运来的有机面膜
That's my organic face mask from Paris.
哦  吼吼吼
Oh, ho ho ho.
特制的布丁啊
Fancy pudding.
对  这是用猩猩的大便做出来的
Yeah. It's made with orangutan poop.
这猴子的伙食真是不错啊
Well, whatever that monkey ate was delicious.
我吃了块香蕉么
Is that banana?
好吧  只要
Okay, just...
恶心哟  乔伊
Eww, Joey...
听好了
Get this.
不知道谁在网上散布了小道消息
Somehow word has spread through the blogosphere
说我可能要饰演《太空狼人》里的特里斯坦
that I'm up for the role of Tristan in "Space Werewolves."
我们绝不知道消息是怎么泄露到网上的
Not sure how that info leaked out onto the Internet.
我们怎么会把这么要紧的大新闻发到
We would never post that juicy tidbit
“史蒂文斯波因特《太空狼人》粉丝群”里
on the Stevens Point "Space Werewolves" fan page
来惹毛这帮狼人粉呢
in hopes of enraging local Tristanites.
丽芙到时候会感谢我所做的一切的
Liv will thank me for this later.
让我猜猜
Let me guess.
你饰演特里斯坦的话  脑残粉们
The fanboys were none too pleased
肯定会把你批判一番的
about you playing Tristan.
你也许要看清形势
You probably want to throw in the towel
知难而退了吧
and back out.
呃  不
Uh, no.
我跟这帮脑子进水的家伙纠结个什么呢
I mean, why do I care what nerd nation
因为我们是一股强大的势力
Because we are a powerful force to be reckoned with...
我是说  他们才是
I mean, they are!
随便吧
Whatever.
这周末我要在纳维尔礼品店店参加
This weekend I have a personal appearance
一个见面会  签售《放声歌唱》的光盘
at Neville's Novelty Shoppe to sign "Sing it Loud!" DVDs.
你们干嘛不跟我来呢
Why don't you guys come with me?
丽芙  纳维尔商店是脑残粉的大本营啊
Liv, Neville's is fanboy central.
如果他们发现你对《太空狼人》的情节一无所知
and then find out that you don't know what you're talking about
就会把你生吞活剥的
they will eat you alive.
这是个生活在太空的狼人故事
He's a werewolf and he lives in space.
我觉得我还需要学习的内容都在这本书里了
I think anything else I need to learn about him will be in here.
我大概周六前就能看完了吧
I can probably finish this by Saturday, yeah?
丽芙  这是第一卷
Liv, that's volume 1.
总共有 64 卷呢
There are 64 volumes.
嗬
Hah!
怪不得他们要把书翻拍成电影
No wonder they're making this into a movie.
谁有工夫看完这么多书啊
Who would want to read all that?